《断头谷》前情提要
Previous on Sleepy Hollow.
安迪  你不是死了吗
Andy? You're supposed to be dead.
骑士不拿到他的头
The Horseman won't stop coming after you
是不会善罢甘休的
until he gets his head.
我妹妹珍妮  她明天就要出院
My sister, Jenny. She's getting out of the institution tomorrow.
黑森佣兵  德国士兵对英国皇室非常忠诚
Hessians. German soldiers loyal to the British Crown.
跟四骑士一样
Like the Horseman.
你杀不死死神  但是你能困住他
You can't kill Death. But you can trap him.
这是你打败他的唯一方法
It's the only way you can defeat him.
克兰
Crane?
就是现在
Now!
好了
Okay.
给你看样东西
I want to show you something.
来顶个拳
Fist bump.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
这是种表达...
It's an expression of...
喜悦的方式
elation.
意味着团队合作
Teamwork.
我们抓到他了
We got him.
顶拳是吧
Huh. Fist bump.
真无聊
Makes no sense.
难以置信
Hard to believe.
简直是不可思议
Impossible.
但我们做到了
And yet, here we are.
我真想给北美防空联合司令部打个电话
I'm tempted to dial in NORAD.
让他们丢个核弹下来  结束这一切
Drop a nuke down here and call it a day.
恐怕他的生命力会跟小强一样顽强
I'm afraid it and the cockroaches will still be standing.
我们已经试过成千上万种方法想要置之死地
We've tried killing this thing a thousand ways to Sunday.
我一枪打中了他的胸膛
I put a bullet in his chest.
甚至砍掉了他的头颅
And cut off his head.
我们在这囚室里布满了克制他的东西
And we filled this cell with his personal Kryptonite.
这些被赋咒语的蜡烛是共济会提供的
Those hex candles from the Mason's supply.
紫外灯是市面上能买到的最强款式
The strongest UV lights on the open market.
-这能削弱他  但...  -他仍然死不了
- It's weakened him, but... - Here he stands before us.
跟两个多世纪前与我交手的那个人
As monstrous as the man I met on the battlefield
一样的可怕
more than two centuries ago.
如果我们消灭不了他  那怎么办
If we can't destroy him, what do you suggest?
让他烂在这么
Let him rot down here?
这个监狱很安全  托马斯・杰斐逊设计的
The cell is secure. Thomas Jefferson designed it.
而且被他妻子所在的女巫集会
Alongside his wife's witch coven,
施以了驱逐邪恶的咒语
who put a supernatural hex around it to keep the evil out.
我很难相信杰斐逊当时预见了
I can hardly believe Jefferson foresaw
这里要囚禁一个无头怪物
holding a headless man prisoner.
他预见的是遍及整个世界
He foresaw holding the worst
最凶恶的恶魔
type of demons that may walk the earth.
毫无疑问  是一种需要他历时多年
A product, no doubt, of his years
才能跟法国人解释明白的产物
trying to reason with the French.
无论无头骑士如何  其他怪物也将降临
No matter what happens with the Horseman, others are coming.
女巫  恶魔  睡魔
Witches, demons, Sandmen.
长官  这听起来很疯狂
Sir, as crazy as this sounds,
但这场战争才刚刚打响
this war has just begun.
也许我们要像对其他战俘一样对他
Then perhaps we treat him as any other captured enemy.
他来断头谷是有原因的
He rode into Sleepy Hollow for a reason.
他知道计划着下一次进攻的邪恶势力是什么
He knows what evil is planning to attack next.
你想审问无头骑士吗
You want to interrogate the Horseman.
我可不觉得他会开口说话
I don't think he's gonna talk.
或者他能与死人交谈
Or maybe he'll talk to someone who's already dead.
这个当然
Of course.
你之前的朋友  布鲁克斯警官
Your former friend, Officer Brooks.
是已故的安迪・布鲁克斯警探吗
As in the late Detective Andy Brooks?
他之前为我们给无头骑士传过口信
He delivered a message to the Horseman for us before.
-他们一定能交流  -我记得他不是死了吗
- They must communicate. - Last I heard, he was dead.
事情不像你想的那样
Rules on that status have gotten a little bendy.
他不幸地被复活了
He's unhappily resurrected.
从而为摩洛克办事儿
Deployed as an agent for Moloch.
摩洛克  是书上说的万恶之首吗
Moloch, the demon on the top of the org chart?
但有个问题  我们怎能相信布鲁克斯呢
Which begs the question: how can we trust Brooks?
我相信他真的很后悔自己的行为
I believe he truly regrets his lot.
他已经帮助我们擒住了无头骑士
He's already aided us in capturing the Horseman.
而且他依然愿意为米尔斯小姐赴汤蹈火
And he still holds unrequited feelings for Ms. Mills.
-真的吗  -长官  我们能找到布鲁克斯
- Seriously? - Sir, we can track down Brooks.
如果你能联系的上我妹妹
If you could get in touch with my sister, I think
我想她能派上用场的
she could be useful.
她不是刚出院吗
Didn't she just get out of Tarrytown Psychiatric?
昨天出的
Yesterday.
她有权知道
She deserves to know.
一个死人  一个精神病人
A dead guy, a mental patient...
还有一个从革命年代穿越来的
and a time traveler from the Revolution.
这就是我们的队伍
That's our team.
我貌似听到只鹿的动静
Thought I heard a deer.
你看到了吗
You see it?
还没
Not yet.
见鬼了吧...
What the hell?
同意
Agreed.
骑士遇到麻烦了
我们需要在此集结队伍
马上
你说的什么  德语吗
What is that, German?
我们最后一次见布鲁克斯是在前面那里
We last saw Brooks in this section up ahead.
这里一定是他的衣柜了
This must be his closet.
比我的大多了
It's bigger than mine,
不得不承认
I'll give him that.
看样子我们的亡灵线人
It appears our undead informant
去城里了
is out on the town.
安迪这个人做事喜欢按习惯来
Andy's a creature of habit.
如果他住在这里的话  那就肯定会回来的
If this is where he lives, this is where he'll come back.
珍妮弗・米尔斯
Jennifer Mills.
我是弗兰克・欧文警监
I'm Captain Frank Irving.
由我接手可以了
I'll take it from here.
警监
Captain.
请问一位无辜的美国人民坐在咖啡厅
I'm all for renditioning innocent Americans
一边喝着豆奶拿铁咖啡
while they're sitting at a cafe,
一边上着网
enjoying a soy latte
你就能因此逮捕人家吗
and some free Wi-Fi.
没有逮捕令  也没有律师在场
No warrant. No lawyer present.
谁让你不接电话
You weren't answering your phone.
是这样啊
Now you see why.
来我办公室
My office.
坐吧
Have a seat.
离开泰瑞顿精神疗养院的第一天
First day out of Tarrytown Psychiatric.
-感觉如何  -我有假释官
- How you doing? - I already have a P.O.
也有心理医生去报告
and a shrink that I report to,
所以不需要别人过问
so I don't need another shoulder.
-你姐姐让我找你的  -那她人呢
- Your sister asked me to find you. - And where's she?
-她有任务在身  -忙的都没时间接电话
- On assignment. - She can't even pick up her phone.
艾比真是没变啊
Typical Abbie, already...
你不喜欢政府权力机构  我懂
You don't like authority. I get it.
我知道你的过去  你说了实话
I know about your past. You told the truth
你跟他们说了你跟你姐姐小时候看到的东西
about what you and your sister saw as kids,
但政府权力机构让你失望了
and the system failed you.
这件事你都知道些什么
What do you know about any of this?
你真的知道她现在在什么地方吗
Do you even really know where she is right now?
艾比让我找你是因为她现在跟无头骑士在一起
Abbie asked me to track you down because she's with the Horseman.
天启四骑士之一
One of the Four Horsemen.
我们抓住他了
We captured him.
"我们"
"We"?
对你姐姐宽容一点吧
Cut your sister some slack.
你联系不到她是有原因的
She got a pretty good excuse for being out of touch.
我要见他
I want to see him.
他现在在共济会的一间牢房里
He's in a Masonic cell
那里应该足够坚固  可以困住他  但是
that's supposed to be strong enough to hold him, but...
这是我有生以来第一次见到这种东西
I've never seen anything like this in my life.
你以前帮过你姐姐
You helped your sister before.
艾比说这件事你能帮上忙  所以让我找你
Abbie wants me to bring you in to this, says you'll be valuable.
我也想相信她  但到目前为止
I'd like to believe her, but so far
你没有给我任何相信的理由
you haven't given me any confidence.
请进
Yeah, come in.
长官  亚当斯古玩店发生了点状况
Sir, there's a situation at Adams Antiquities.
公共设施问题
10-65 in progress.
报警公司打电话报警的
Alarm company called it in.
亚当斯
Adams?
你知道这个地方吗
You know the place?
我以前在店主手下工作过
Yeah, I used to do work for the owner.
自由收购
Freelance acquisitions.
收购什么
What kind of acquisitions?
好吧
Fine.
在这乖乖等我回来
Stay put till I get back.
等一下
Wait.
等等
Hey.
你想让我干什么
What do you want from me?
你看到这些人了吗
Do you see these people?
他们不懂
They don't understand.
我希望他们永远都不用懂
Hopefully they never will.
至少有我在时不用  但我也是新手
At least not on my watch. But I'm new to this,
而你在过去十二年的时间里
and you've spent the last 12 years of your life
都在考虑魔鬼出现的那一天
thinking about the day the demons will rise.
你可以自己去对付他  也可以帮我们一起对付
You can go it alone or you can help us.
但是我需要知道
But I need to know:
你是帮我们还是不帮
are you in or out?
帮
In.
那我们一起走吧
Then let's take a ride.
《变形记》
Metamorphosis.
挺适合布鲁克斯的
It's appropriate for Brooks.
你也该看看
You should check it out, too.
过去两百年里出现了很多好的
You know, there's been some pretty good American literature
-美国文学作品  -是啊
- in the last 200 years. - Yes,
我发现有吐温
I've discovered Twain,
福克纳  很厉害的南方人
Faulkner-- fascinating Southerner.
虽然我们应该谈论的是...
Though we should discuss...
书
books.
这是埃及象形文字
These are Egyptian hieroglyphs.
-放下  -安迪
- Put that down! - Andy.
艾比  你来这里干嘛  他怎么会来这里
Abbie. What are you doing here? What's he doing here?
我们一直都在找你
We've been looking for you.
希望你能帮我们
We're hoping you can help us.
我已经告诉你困住骑士的方法了
I already told you how to trap the Horseman.
你不是抓到他了吗
You have him, don't you?
但我们要知道他的弱点
We want to know his weakness.
我们要怎样才能打倒他
How do we break him?
打不倒
You don't.
你打不倒他
You don't break him.
别管他就是了
You leave him be.
唯一能和他沟通的办法
There is a way to communicate with him.
就是通过你
Through you.
这些是埃及人和死神沟通的标志
These are Egyptian symbols for communicating with the dead.
你是他的巫师
You're his necromancer.
巫师
Necromancer?
被指定的人拥有与死神对话的力量
An appointed one who has the power to speak for the dead.
你就是他的声音代言人吧
You're his voice, aren't you?
是的
I am.
那这就是你赎罪的机会
Then this is your chance at redemption.
和我们一起
Come with us,
让我们揭露他的秘密
allow us to unearth the man within.
你要带布鲁克斯回牢里吗
You want to bring Brooks to the cell?
是的  让他与骑士对话
Yes, to speak to the Horseman.
虽然有失败的风险  但我们不得不这么做
It's a calculated risk but one we must take
才能在这场战争中取得进展
to gain ground in this war.
我们会采取一切防范措施
We'll take every precaution.
艾比  请不要逼我
Abbie, please don't make me do this.
你说过你想帮我
You said you wanted to help me.
是的
I do.
但是你得明白
But you got to understand,
我在活着的时候  所作出的决定
the decisions I made when I was alive,
是不能反悔的
I can't take back.
我的灵魂再也不属于我自己
My soul doesn't belong to me anymore.
你的灵魂归我所有
当他来的时候
When he visits...
我毫无选择  只能服从他的命令
I have no choice but to obey his commands.
在我力所能及的时候
I help you
我会帮助你
when I can,
但是如果你把我和他关在一起
but if you put me in there with him,
结果会很糟糕
it is not gonna end well.
我怎么知道我现在能相信你
How do I know I can even trust you now?
你不能
You can't.
但是相信这句话
But believe this:
面对死神...
Confronting Death...
带来的只有痛苦
leads to nothing but misery.
这个黑暗将会永远萦绕着你
It's a darkness that'll haunt you forever.
好了
All right.
这边请
This way.
拜托了
Please.
错了  抱歉
No. Apologies.
应该是这边
It's this way.
手离远点
Hey. Hands in the open.
他们打破了珠宝盒
They broke the jewelry case
却没拿走这些价值连城的首饰
and left all the most expensive stuff.
这一切看起来像是
This all just seems...
幌子吗
Fake?
声东击西  但是为什么呢
A diversion, but why?
我要给你看些东西
I got to show you something.
通常亚当斯把他最贵重的物品藏在这里
Adams used to hide his most valuable merch in here.
-珍妮...  -亚当斯
- Jenny... - Adams!
他中枪了
He's shot!
这里需要个医务人员
Get a medic in here.
过来这边
Over here.
把第二个架子上的盒子拿过来
Second shelf. The box. Bring it over.
他们得手了吗
Did they get it?
盒子是空的
It's empty.
这是十六世纪督德鲁伊教徒的手稿
16th century Druidic scripture.
里面有什么
What was in it?
有色雷斯盘
Thracian Phiale.
一个古老的残遗物  据说在克伦威尔
A ancient relic, allegedly protected by warlocks
征服英国之后  此盘由术士保护
after Cromwell's conquest of Britain.
怎么会有人想要这种东西
Why would someone want something like that?
你不会想要
You wouldn't.
除非你想要打破降咒魔法
Not unless you wanted to break a Hax-Spell.
就像保护骑士牢房的那个咒语
Like the one protecting the Horseman's cell.
是谁干的
Who did this?
他们之间讲的是德语
They spoke German to each other.
是黑森佣兵
Hessians.
去吧
Go.
-去吧  -快点
- Go. - Come on.
如果黑森佣兵知道骑士的所在地
If the Hessians know where the Horseman is,
他们就能用这个盘子解除降咒
they can use the Phiale to remove the Hex.
我们把骑士照在紫外线灯下
We've got the Horseman weak
他们就会失去能力
under the U.V. lights.
除非他们把电力切断
Not if they cut the power.
他们下一步就要破坏电网
They're gonna take out the grid next.
我们要在去的路上打电话给艾比
We need to call Abbie on the way.
别说我没警告过你
Consider yourself warned.
你说过了
Considered.
主人  请听吾之召唤
赐吾汝之声
他好像没有聊天的兴致  你该感到庆幸
Must not be feeling too chatty. Consider it a blessing.
提不起精神吗
Feeling less than robust?
很好
Good.
你有名字吗
So, do you have a name?
还是我就这么叫你"死神"
Should I just call you Death?
或许你伺奉着摩洛克
You may serve Moloch...
或许在这牢房之外
and outside these walls you may be
你是《启示录》中的四骑士之一
one of the Four Horsemen from the Book of Revelation,
但如今...
but now...
你只是一个囚徒
you are nothing but a prisoner.
我会亲眼见证你与你同类的溃败
And I will see you and your kind defeated.
正如我亲手取了你的首级一样
Just as I took your head.
无论用什么方式
One way or other,
我都将得知你的秘密
I will learn your secrets,
而你将永世被困在这里
and you shall remain here for eternity...
...永远的失败者
...A failure.
这是从哪里来的
Where'd that come from?
克兰
Crane.
这是属于...
It belonged...
卡特里娜的
to Katrina.
是的
Yes,
你虽砍下了我的头颅
you took my head,
但死神不会因此而缄默
but death will not be silenced.
克兰  我知道你在想什么
Crane, I know what you're thinking.
你不会知道我在想些什么
You have no idea what I'm thinking.
听着  我是站在你这边的
Look, I'm on your side here.
布鲁克斯说过他会试图激怒我们
Brooks warned us that he would try to get under our skin.
但骑士为什么会有卡特里娜的项链
But how does the Horseman have Katrina's necklace?
好吧
Okay,
让我们从已知的信息着手
let's start with what we know.
为什么骑士会有这条项链
Why would he have this exact necklace?
这是送给她的一份礼物
It was a gift to her.
但不是我送的
But not from me.
这是她曾经的订婚对象送给她的
It was given to her by the man to whom she was once betrothed.
我的挚友
My best friend,
亚伯拉罕・范・布朗特
Abraham Van Brunt.
这条项链一定会虏获她的心  先生
This one, sir, is sure to melt her heart.
您在殖民地里再找不出一条这样的项链了
There's no other like it in the colonies.
我想这条项链一定会很适合她
I think I rather like it for her.
你觉得怎么样  伊卡伯德
What do you think, Ichabod?
是的  它...很漂亮
Yes, it's a... it's a beautiful piece.
这是最好的一条了
It's the best one.
这不是我该做的决定
It's not my place.
伊卡伯德  这很重要
Ichabod, this is important.
我...不确定这是否适合卡特里娜
I'm... I'm not sure it suits Katrina.
这条不错
This one.
能衬托出她的优雅
It embodies her elegance,
简单  美貌
simplicity, beauty...
和内敛
and restraint.
那好吧
Uh, very well.
我相信你的眼光
I'm trusting you.
转过身去  亲爱的
Turn around, darling.
喜欢吗
There... we... go.
太完美了
It's perfect.
这正是我喜欢的款式
Exactly what I would have chosen.
我就知道你一定会喜欢
I knew it would be.
拉特利奇来了
Ah, Rutledge is here,
他一定是带来了英国皇室的消息
with news from the Crown.
有传言说皇室正派部队前来消灭议会
Word is they're sending troops to disrupt Congress.
母亲
Mother.
恕我们失陪一阵
Excuse us.
项链是你挑的  不是吗
You picked this out, didn't you?
-你说什么  -亚伯拉罕的品味太浮夸
- Sorry? - Abraham's taste is far more excessive.
他绝不会送这样的东西给我
He's not bought anything of the kind for me.
或许他正在试着学习你的喜好
Perhaps he's learning.
我只是提供了一些建议
I merely consulted.
别太在意
Take no offense.
我要取消这个婚约
I'm breaking off the engagement.
你不能这样做
You can't.
我今晚就会告诉亚伯拉罕
I'm telling Abraham tonight.
卡特里娜...
Katrina...
我知道包办婚姻并不像童话故事般美好
I know an arranged marriage is not the stuff of fairy tales,
但亚伯拉罕来自一个良好的家庭  而且...
but Abraham's from a good family, and...
他爱你
he loves you.
但我不爱他
I do not love him.
我从未爱过他
I never have.
我的心另有所属
My heart belongs to another.
我不能背叛我的朋友
I cannot betray my friend.
这事不关乎你  亲爱的伊卡伯德
This isn't about you, dear Ichabod.
这关系着我的人生
This is my life.
我要取消这个婚约
I am breaking off the engagement
是因为我不想这样
because it isn't right for me.
-这么做会有后果的  -记得吗
- There are consequences. - As there were
在你背叛英格兰时不也正是如此
when you turned your back on England, remember?
这一切
All of this...
都是我们要努力留给后人的宝贵财富
it's the remnants of the life we are fighting to leave behind.
我可不希望自己努力建立的独立国家
I do not wish to go to the effort of creating
到头来还要被毫无意义的旧俗所桎梏
an independent country only to have it dictated by the same
正如我们祖国的传统
senseless customs as our motherland.
如果我要结婚
If and when I marry,
那一定是因为爱
it will be out of love.
否则  我都不知道自己在为何而战
Otherwise, I know not what I'm fighting for.
你完全有资格获得爱
You deserve nothing less than love.
我爱你  伊卡伯德
And I love you, Ichabod.
她甩了她的未婚夫  为了你
She dumped her fiance? For you.
你可真有几把刷子
Wow. You got some game.
我既没那个贼心也没那个贼胆
I neither wanted nor did I invite "Game."
这种不幸的情况
The unfortunate situation was a by-product
是当时女权极端贫乏的产物
of the meager rights afforded to women at the time.
但选了你还是好一些
It's still better to be you.
无论如何...
Be that as it may...
我得知道天启骑士是怎么拿到的
I need to understand why the Horseman has it.
是不是从她那里拿的
Did he take it from her?
他知不知道摩洛克为何要囚禁卡特里娜
Does he know why Moloch holds Katrina captive?
我们得关注重点
We need to stay on point.
我们在找他的弱点
We are looking for his weakness.
别让他发现你的弱点
Don't let him find yours.
那我们就来找找吧
And we shall find it.
让他开口
We have him talking.
断头谷电厂  西区电网
这就是为什么电厂工人都不配武器
That's why no electrical workers carry firearms.
在这儿等着
Wait here.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
不许动
Don't move.
这么快就等得不耐烦了
So much for her waiting.
把枪放下  马上
Put 'em down! Now!
我们的人数比你多多了
You're way outnumbered.
换做我就会乖乖听她话
I'd do exactly as she said.
二对四吗
Two against four?
我觉得我们胜算更大
I like our odds.
再好好数数  阿道夫
Check your math, Adolf.
把手放在头上
Now, put your hands behind your head.
你怎么拿到这条项链的
How did you acquire this necklace?
你想戴上吗
You wish to wear it?
你怎么戴得上啊
How would that work, exactly?
你想念卡特里娜了
You miss Katrina.
关于她你知道些什么
What do you know about her?
我知道她所有的秘密
I know all of her secrets.
她的命运  她的定数
Her fate. Her destiny.
好  那跟我说说
Well, tell me.
你希望我知道的  不是吗
You want me to know, don't you?
还不到时候
Not yet.
但是你会知道的  在你死前
But you will learn... before you die.
我在战场上打败了你
I bested you in battle.
日光削弱了你的力量
The sunlight has weakened you.
你必须用一个傀儡来传话
You must use a puppet to speak.
而你现在像个笼中困兽
And now you are caged like a beast,
因为
because...
我取了你的项上人头
I took your head.
我打败了你们  在战场上打败了你们
I took you! I took you on the battlefield!
我杀了你的共济会弟兄
I slayed your Mason brethren!
把他们的脑袋当灯笼挂
I hung their heads like lanterns!
我杀了她的搭档
I killed her partner!
我也会杀了你
And I will kill you.
天呐  变成私人恩怨了
My, this has become very personal.
为什么是我
Why me?
你的任务是屠杀共济会  可你逗留在这里
Your mission was to massacre the Masons, yet you lingered.
为了你的头颅吗
For your head?
不
No.
为了我
For me.
对你来说那是巨大的打击
That was your downfall.
摩洛克批准这个任务了吗
Did Moloch sanction this mission?
还是说你自作主张
Are you on your own?
有些东西影响了你的判断力
Something blinded your judgment...
让你变得不够谨慎
made you careless.
我一直在等待这一天
I have waited for this day.
受到华盛顿嘉奖的士兵
Washington's prize soldier--
你在战场上搜寻我的同时
all the time you were searching for me on the battlefield...
我也在搜寻你
...I, too, was searching for you.
你就是我的任务
You were my mission.
无论过去还是现在
Then and now.
你问我为什么留在这里
You ask why I remain here.
是为了了结我的任务
To finish what I started.
当你垂死的时候
And as you lay dying,
想想紧随其后的鲜血与杀戮
think about all the bloodshed that will follow,
那都是你一手造成的
and know that it will be on your hands.
米尔斯  那辆货车是证物
Mills, that van is evidence.
你知道这有多危险吗
Do you know how dangerous this is?
我出动了一整支特种部队
I have an entire TAC team in position.
所以我才不担心
That's why I wasn't worried.
下次我再让你等着的时候
The next time I tell you to wait...
包是空的
This bag is empty.
袋子里装着的东西被转移到别处了
Whatever was in it is somewhere else out here now.
各单位注意
Attention,
我需要警犬在现场西南角立即展开搜索
I need the dogs rolling over the southwest quadrant immediately.
你为什么要在战场上找我
Why were you searching for me on the battlefield?
为你搭档的死报仇
To avenge the death of your partner.
我的搭档
My partner?
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
难道你已经忘了他吗
Have you forgotten about him already?
克兰
Crane.
另一位见证者知道
Does the other Witness know
你背叛并杀害了自己以前的搭档吗
that you betrayed and killed your former partner?
不  一派胡言
No. That's lies.
这根本不是事实
That's not what happened!
克兰  听我说
Crane, listen to me.
我还没审完  女中尉
I'm not finished, Lieutenant.
警监
Captain.
我在现场周围发现了这个
Found this on the perimeter.
全体注意  断头谷水电部技术人员...
All teams, S&R on Hollow DWP...
紫外灯灭了
U.V. Lights.
我早说了不会顺利的
I told you this wasn't gonna end well.
所以警监相信还是这些
And the captain believes these same Hessians
黑森佣兵们偷了那个东西吗
are responsible for stealing this artifact?
我们只是不知道确切的人数
We just don't know how many of these guys there are.
他在水电部逮捕了六个人
He arrested six at the DWP.
说全称行吗
Uh, acronyms.
水务与电力部门
Department of Water & Power.
而且我们预计  距离重新恢复供电
And we're still guessing it's two hours
还有两小时
until they get the power back on.
两小时吗
Two hours?
他的力量每时每刻都在加强
Every minute he grows stronger.
他们会试着解救无头骑士的
They will attempt to release the Horseman.
我们已经准备好了  欧文正在来的路上
We'll be ready for them. Irving's on his way.
我要进去继续审问他
I'm going to resume our interrogation.
别急  我能看出来  他触动了你的神经
Not yet. Clearly, he struck a nerve in there.
我没有杀亚伯拉罕
I didn't kill Abraham.
我相信你  但我要了解他到底在说什么
I believe you, but I need to know what he's talking about.
想告诉我吗
Want to fill me in?
当卡特里娜打破婚约之后  亚伯拉罕伤心欲绝
Abraham was devastated when Katrina broke her troth to him.
第二天
The next day,
我们俩被委派去执行一项重要的秘密任务
the two of us were charged with an important clandestine mission,
去护送
to deliver
《第一届大陆会议决议宣言》
the Declaration of Resolves of the First Continental Congress.
《决议宣言》
Declaration of Resolves?
就是《独立宣言》的前身吗
Was that a precursor to the Declaration of Independence?
是的
Indeed.
它向国王描述了我们的怨愤和不满
It outlined our grievances to the king.
这是一项充满危险的重任
It was a crucial errand fraught with danger.
但是亚伯拉罕一直心不在焉
But Abraham's mind was elsewhere.
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
小心一点  我们可是在敌占区
Be cautious-- we're in enemy territory.
她不想嫁给我
She doesn't want to marry me.
-真抱歉  -是我对她不好吗  克兰
- I'm sorry. - Did I mistreat her, Crane?
是我不够富有
Have I not enough wealth
没法给她的家人奢侈安逸的生活吗
to keep her family in comfort, even luxury?
没法给她显赫的社会地位吗
Social status she clearly has never had.
卡特里娜从不看重这些
Katrina's never cared for those things.
她充满生气  随心所欲
She's spirited. She's motivated by the heart.
随心所欲
The heart?
她没权利这么做
She has no right.
她这么做会让我怎么想
Do you realize how this will make me look?
是我配不上她吗
That I am not good enough for her?
我也是昨天才知道的  我发誓
I did not know until yesterday, I swear.
她向我...表达了自己的爱意
She professed her love... to me.
向你吗
To you?
强扭的瓜不甜
There's no need to force an unhappy union,
以你的身份和前景  有很多女人都愿意
not when there are many women who would faint
-投怀送抱...  -别一副...
- at your prospect... - Do not...
神气十足的样子
patronize me.
你追求她多久了
How long have you been wooing her?
亚伯拉罕  不  我绝不会拿我们的友情...
Abraham, no, I would not do our friendship the dishonor...
但你还是做了  你做了
But you have. You have!
亚伯拉罕...
Abraham...
你是我的朋友
you are my friend.
现在  请你理解  这对大家来说都不好受
Now, please, you must understand, this is hard for us all.
我们还想得到你的祝福
We wish for your blessing.
别想太多了
Do not burden yourself.
亚伯拉罕  不管你对我有多忿恨
Abraham, whatever your misgivings,
别在这时候发泄  别在这里
now is not the time, not here.
我们还有任务
Our mission.
满口胡言
Lies!
-拔出你的剑  -亚伯拉罕  我不跟你决斗
- Draw your sword. - Abraham, I will not duel.
你觉得我不配和你决斗吗  拔剑吧
You don't deem me worthy? Arm yourself!
-我认输  认输好吗  -我不接受
- I yield. I yield. - I do not accept.
现在是谁不配了
Who's unworthy now?
-亚伯拉罕  挺住  -走  快走
- Abraham, oh, no. - Leave, leave.
我们必须要平安护送《决议宣言》
We must deliver the Declaration.
快走
Leave me!
我不想伤害他的
I never meant to hurt him.
他的自尊
His pride
最终害了他自己
came at a great cost.
杀了他的是黑森雇佣兵  不是我
The Hessians killed him, not me.
布鲁克斯警告过我们
This is exactly what Brooks warned.
他知道你最黑暗的秘密
He knows your darkest secrets.
我也要发掘他的秘密
And I will learn his.
现在不行  他正在逐渐变强
Not yet. Not while he's getting stronger.
那我就更要...
That's all the more reason for me...
坐下来
For you to sit down.
我的审问有进展
I'm making progress.
现在我们知道了他为什么杀死了
Now we know why remained in Sleepy Hollow
共济会会员后还留在断头谷
after killing the Masons.
没错  为了杀你
Yes. To kill you.
只有知道他要杀我的原因才能找到他的弱点
And understanding why is key to learning his weakness.
克兰
Crane,
我们都知道该怎么审讯犯人
we both know how interrogations work.
对方若是揭了你的伤疤  就不该再继续
You don't face your adversary when you're raw
你就是这么失控的
that is how you lose control.
我没失控
I am in control!
艾比  克兰  我是欧文
Abbie? Crane? It's Irving.
我们尽快赶来了
We came as soon as we could.
我们
We?
我们查了所有黑森佣兵
We searched all the Hessians.
他们都没有色雷斯盘
None of them have the Thracian Phiale.
你把她也扯进来了
You brought her down?
我在帮警监的忙
I'm helping out the captain.
我说的是告诉她情况  不是带她来
I said tell her about it, not introduce them.
-你知道这是她出院第一天  -是吗
- You understand this is her first day out. - Do I?
如果他们都没有色雷斯盘
If none of them have the Thracian Phiale,
那它在哪里
where is it?
我们搜查了他们的家
We're searching their homes,
不动产  能想到的地方都搜遍了
properties, any connection we can think of.
目前仍一无所获
Nothing so far.
那玩意怎样才能生效
How does this thing work, exactly?
珍妮
Jenny.
对...
Right. Um...
他们得闯入牢房
they'd have to break into the cell
然后施展德鲁伊教的咒语
and perform a Druidic incantation.
就能解除巫法
That will lift the hex,
而所有的邪恶力量都会来到他身边
and all kinds of bad could get down here with him.
-我去叫后援  -别
- I'm calling for backup. - No.
她说得对  那可能就正好中了黑森佣兵的计
She's right. That may be exactly what the Hessians want.
已经有一个出卖灵魂的警察了
We already know of one dirty cop.
我们不知道能相信谁
We have no idea who we can trust
让外人进来会置我们于死地
Letting anyone into the tunnels with us could be the death of us.
恐怕她们说得对
I'm afraid they may be right.
这是一场秘密战争
This is a secret war.
挑选战友时要谨慎
We must be cautious whom we invite into it.
好吧
Fine.
我会在每个入口都布置一支特种兵队
I'll station an armed TAC team at every access point.
禁止任何人下来
Nobody's getting down here.
骑士出不去的  女中尉
The Horseman's not going anywhere, Lieutenant.
除非先杀了我
Not whilst I'm still alive.
好吧
All right,
如果只有我们守这里  那得需要重型火炮
if it's just us down here, we're gonna need heavier artillery.
我不会独留他一人在这
I'm not leaving the prisoner unmanned.
那你就留在这  坚守岗位
Then you can stay behind. Hold the fort.
你们两个帮我拿武器
But you two can help me carry the weapons.
长官
Sir...
没事的
It's all right.
还有巫法保护着牢房
The cell is still protected by the hex.
留你俩在一起我不放心  克兰
I don't like leaving you with him, Crane.
没有选择了
I see no alternative.
我不能留他单独在这里
I'm not leaving him alone.
我们走得越早
Sooner we leave,
回来得越早
sooner we're back.
我们待在隧道里  你俩去拿武器
We'll stay in the tunnels.You go to the precinct.
我会联系还驻守在电网的特种部队
I'll connect with the TAC team at the top of the grid.
一切顺利
Godspeed.
警监
Captain.
克兰  我留下来陪你
Crane, I'm staying back here with you.
不用了  女中尉
I'm fine, Lieutenant.
谢谢
Thank you.
别失了风度
Just don't lose your cool.
我永远不会
Oh. I shall never...
"失了风度"
"Lose my cool."
如果布鲁克斯攻击你的话
If Brooks gives you any flack,
把他的头也砍下来
take his head, too.
他好可怕
He is damn scary.
对  起码他现在还被锁着
Yeah. And you saw him locked up.
想象他骑在马上  拿着一把M4卡宾枪对着你
Imagine him on a horse, pointing an M4 at your ass.
他干过这事吗
He did that?
前几周不寻常的事我见多了
I've seen a lot of things in the last few weeks.
也许我们成功了
Well, maybe if we do this right,
那些东西就不会来了
those things'll stop coming.
色雷斯教徒...
我用魔盘
解除所有约束咒语
我召唤你们...
摩洛克奴仆请现身...
该死的那是什么
What the hell was that?
珍妮
Jenny!
这场秘密战争再次开始了
So, the secret war has begun anew.
你的任务是屠杀共济会会员
You were sent on a mission to kill the Masons.
你成功了
You succeeded.
但后来却忤逆了你的主人
But then you disobeyed your master
因为你有自己的任务
because you had your own mission.
是什么让你甘冒永囚地狱之险
What caused you to risk eternal imprisonment?
你与我有何未解的恩怨
What is your unfinished business with me?
现在  伊卡伯德
Now, Ichabod,
你马上就知道了
you shall learn.
布鲁克斯
Brooks.
不
No.
你搞了什么鬼
What have you done?
我别无选择
I had no choice!
根本不受我的意志所控
It wasn't my decision!
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
这怎么可能
How can this be?
亚伯拉罕
Abraham?
这不可能
This is impossible.
你看着亚伯拉罕死去
You watched Abraham die.
那只不过是开始
That was only the beginning.
之后他来找我
Then he came to me.
你跟恶魔做了交易
You made a deal with the Devil.
他给了我一直想要的东西
He gave me what I always wanted.
复仇
Revenge.
我的战利品可不是复仇
My prize is not revenge.
是卡特里娜
It is Katrina.
卡特里娜
Katrina?
我想我知道自己被困在这里的原因
I believe I know why I am here.
她被囚禁...
She's held captive...
是因为你
for you.
她的灵魂...
Her soul...
会再一次属于我
will be mine once more.
不
No.
黑暗之影
进入房间
保护骑士
停  你不能杀他
Stop! You can't kill him!
主人不允许
The master forbids it!
告诉艾比我很抱歉
Tell Abbie I'm sorry.
导致亚伯拉罕成为天启骑士的并不是你
You didn't cause Abraham to become the Horseman.
不  是我
Yes, I did.
我亵渎了他的荣誉
I violated his honor.
这个太老套了
That is so 18th century.
人们会自己做决定
People make their own decisions.
你不必为他的行为负责
You are not responsible for his actions.
不用吗
No?
我对卡特里娜的爱蒙蔽了我
I was so blinded by my love for Katrina
我咎由自取
I created my own nemesis.
你这么说也太自大了
That is your arrogance talking.
怎么了
What?
我总觉得亚伯拉罕很自大
I always found Abraham arrogant.
但也许...
But perhaps...
他其实是我在镜中的倒影
he was just a mirror to myself.
说实话  我更喜欢烛光
Truth be told, I prefer candlelight.
它能营造一种氛围
It sets a certain mood.
布拉姆本可以杀了我以了心愿
Bram could've quenched his desire to kill me,
但布鲁克斯和摩洛克的奴仆阻止了他
but Brooks and Moloch's minions stopped him.
我无法解释摩洛克为何会帮我摆脱天启骑士
I can't explain why Moloch spared me from the Horseman.
或许  你只是不该死在他手上
Other than maybe you are not his to kill.
如果我不该由死亡骑士处置
If I'm not meant for the Horseman of Death,
那该由谁来
then who?
骑士说卡特里娜的灵魂将会是他的
The Horseman said that Katrina's soul will be his.
"将"这个字至关重要
"Will" being the crucial word.
所以也许
So perhaps...
也许等他和其他骑士一起重返马背
perhaps she's being held
她就能脱离囚禁了
until he rides with the other Horsemen.
从此末日便会开始
Thus beginning the end of days.
我们面对的是我们远不能控制的力量
We're dealing with forces so beyond our control.
远远不能
Beyond beyond.
可是...
And yet...
什么
Yes?
如果卡特里娜作为骑士的战利品被囚禁
If Katrina is being held for the Horseman as his prize
而亚伯拉罕想除你而后快
and Abraham was willing to go rogue and kill you,
所以出卖他的灵魂来...困住她...
sell his soul to... trap her...
那我们就找到了骑士的弱点
Then we've found the Horseman's weakness.
我妻子
My wife.
这就是关键  中尉
That's the key, Lieutenant.
现在  我们更加需要卡特里娜了
Now, more than ever... we need Katrina.
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译  Roaddog&
Slience
翻译  暴龙蛋&
胖兔纯
翻译 断头欠&
圈圈
翻译 卫老哥&
meatloaf
校对  米小勒&
swears
时间轴   imok&
新月照坟场
后期  吉吉
断头谷
第一季  第八集
总监  米小勒&
swears